《诉讼双雄》前情提要
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
一个警卫对监狱的事情
There was a guard who was getting suspicious
起了疑心
of what was going on in there.
他们想让我解决了他
They wanted me to put him down.
首席翻译官
█ 网易见外
我跟他们说我不做
I told them I wouldn't do it
直到他们的老大直接找到了我
until whoever was running the show came to me directly.
那人是谁
And who exactly was that?
首席校对官
人人译视界
·
人人
罗杰·夏皮罗  改造公司的首席执行官
Roger Shapiro-- CEO of Reform Corp.
-然后发生了什么  -我杀了他
- And then what happened? - I killed him.
翻译     Alex 辰星晓Reginamoon 木浅
所以你俩是合起伙来整我是吗
So you two are in on this together.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
翻译     海云生 异羽  arcadiachi huiyi
你从此以后再不能对犯人做这种烂事
You're never gonna pull this shit again on prisoners.
这是罗杰·夏皮罗的签字认罪书
That's a signed confession from Roger Shapiro,
校对     木浅
上面写着他参与了阴谋
saying he entered into a conspiracy
而这阴谋就是你一手策划的
and that conspiracy was arranged by you.
你们也不能站这儿
I'm not going to stand here
时间轴     张小满    Caroline
等我写辞职信吧
and write my resignation letter in front of you two.
你和布莱恩是怎么回事
What's going on with you and Brian?
唐娜  他结婚了  我决不会那么做的
Donna, he's married. I would never do it.
后期     斯人
我知道  但我也知道并不是
I know, but I also know that the heart doesn't always listen
大脑说决不能如何心就会照办的
to what the brain says it would never do.
总监     木浅
-丹妮斯·加洛吗  -你是谁
- Denise Gallo? - Who are you?
认识你父亲的一个人  他要我把这个给你
Someone who knew your father. He wanted you to have this.
┌
┐
└
┘
人人影视官方客户端
唯一下载渠道
app.YYeTs.com
-你知不知道  -知道什么
- Did you know? - Know what?
┌
┐
└
┘
盖文·安德鲁本来要找我给他洗钱
That Gavin Andrews was gonna ask me to launder money for him?
我知道他有事找你做
I knew he was gonna ask you to do something.
帮我脱身
Help me get out of this.
你用我的钱干了什么
What the hell did you do with my money?
我给你找到了一个不错的商业机会
I found you a legitimate business opportunity.
-你被炒了  -我不这么觉得
- You're fired. - I don't think so.
因为如果我能这么对你
Because if I can do this to you,
想象一下我为了你能做什么吧
imagine what I can do for you.
-你好  -总算打通了
- Hello. - There you are.
你什么时候来办公室
What the hell time do you get to the office?
我每天早上提前十分钟到办公室
I'm at my desk ten minutes before I need to be every morning,
这意味着你已经找过我了
which means you tracked me down.
问题是  你有什么事
The question is, why?
因为我们有麻烦了
Because we've got a situation.
-你做了什么  -我什么也没做
- What did you do now? - I didn't do anything.
我有架运输机携带了几幅画
One of my transport flights was carrying some art.
由于船体失压
Apparently the hull depressurized,
有一幅画出现了破损
and one of the pieces got damaged.
-哪种画  -很名贵的那种
- What kind of art? - The expensive kind.
那画一定上保险了吧  应该没什么问题
Well, then it had to be insured, so what's the problem?
问题是保险检验员刚走
The problem is the insurance inspector just left here,
那个混蛋竟然撂下狠话
and the son of a bitch has got the balls to say
他们要因损坏起诉我
they'd be suing me for the damages.
没事  我来处理  是哪家保险公司
All right, I'll get into it. Who's the insurance company?
-德克哈特保险集团  -该死
- Dexhart Insurance Group. - Shit.
出了什么事  有什么问题吗
What's the matter? Is that gonna be a problem?
先告诉我  你收到他们的传票了吗
Just tell me, have they filed the papers yet?
你以为我为什么这么早找你
Why do you think I'm calling you this early?
路易
Louis.
这太傻了  你要带我去哪儿
This is silly. Where are you taking me?
放松  我们到了
Relax. We're there.
我能把眼罩摘了吗
Then can I take off this blindfold?
不能  除非你能猜到我们现在在哪儿
No. Not until you guess exactly where we are right now.
我们在我的新办公室
We're in my new office.
你怎么  你怎么会知道
What the f-- How could you know that?
因为你告诉过我下季度我要升高级合伙人
Because you told me I'd make senior partner next quarter,
如今时间到了
and it's next quarter.
我现在能把眼罩摘了吧
Now can I take this blindfold off?
该死  你把气氛都给破坏掉了  对吧
Holy shit, you just suck the fun out of everything, don't you?
这样的话
In that case,
我从九岁的时候
I have dreamt about making senior partner
就梦想成为高级合伙人
since I was nine years old.
你不仅帮我达成了这个心愿...
You not only fought for me to get this...
如果不是你我都进不了这家律所
I wouldn't even be at this firm without you.
最重要的是  路易...
And on top of all that, Louis...
这间办公室是我见过的最美的地方
this office is the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
好吧  是我错了
All right. I was wrong.
你还是蛮有意思的
You don't suck the fun out of anything.
谢谢你  路易  谢谢你为我做的一切
Thank you, Louis. Thank you for fighting for me.
-萨曼莎  我们得谈谈  -我猜猜
- Samantha, we need to talk. - Let me guess--
-盖文给你打电话了  -没错
- Gavin called you. - He did.
那你应该知道我们有利益冲突
Then you know we have a conflict,
这就意味着我们有人要退出这个案子
which means one of us has to drop their client.
所以你有盖文私人联系方式吗
So do you have Gavin's private line,
还是需要我告诉你
or do you need me to give it to you?
我什么也不需要  因为你会打电话
I don't need anything, because you're gonna call up
给德克哈特保险  告诉他们你不能接手
Dexhart Insurance and tell them you can't handle
-这件案子  -你在跟我开玩笑吗
- this particular matter. - Are you kidding me?
如果不是因为我盖文不可能成为你的客户
You wouldn't even have Gavin if it weren't for me.
我如何成为他的律师不重要  我不能丢下他
It doesn't matter how I got him--I'm not dropping him.
亚历克斯  我告诉过你
Alex, I told you,
那家伙不值得你惹祸上身
the guy isn't worth the trouble.
把这件事当成一个
View this is an opportunity
摆脱他和他划清界限的机会
to cut him loose and be done with it.
等等  是你的客户告诉你他们想起诉我们
Wait a second. Did your client say they wanted to sue mine,
-还是你建议他们这么做  -这有区别吗
- or did you suggest it to them? - What difference does it make?
区别在于我以为我们已经讲和了
The difference is I thought we were past this.
倘若这是你为提名合伙人玩的把戏
But if this is how you're making your play for name partner,
-那是没用的  -我唯一玩的把戏就是
- it's not gonna work. - The only play I'm making
保护我的当事人免受你的当事人伤害
is to protect my client from yours,
因为是盖文蓄意破坏的那架飞机
because Gavin sabotaged that plane,
肯定是他  我了解他干的那些事
and I know that because I know everything else he's done.
你刚自承利用职务信息
And you just admitted using privileged information
损害前委托人的利益
against a former client.
我用这个就能把你从这案子里撵出去
And I could have you tossed off this just for that.
你是说类似利用你当事人的家人
You mean information like using a member
对抗你的当事人这种职务信息吗
of your client's family against them?
那不算泄露职务信息  你明知道
That's not breaking privilege, and you know it.
在那混蛋干坏事时抓个现行
And neither is catching that asshole
也不算是泄露职务信息
with his hand in the cookie jar.
废话少说  萨曼莎  别管这事
Cut the bullshit, Samantha, and step out of the ring,
因为无论你多想做到  这都是不可能的
because this isn't happening no matter how much you want it to.
不是我想做到  是我的当事人想
I don't want it. My client does.
并且我这辈子都不会不战而退
And I've never stepped out of a ring in my life.
你要么打电话给盖文  要么找人顶替你
So either call Gavin or someone can do it for you,
因为这案子不会撤销
because this case is moving forward.
你给自己搭了个不错的窝啊  罗伯特
Nice home you've made for yourself here, Robert.
起码比你应该住的地方强  汤米
Nicer than the home you should have, Tommy,
因为你该进监狱
since you belong in prison.
你居然提起这个  这可真有趣
Funny you should say that,
因为我正是为此事而来的
'cause that's exactly why I'm here.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我说的是你把我
I'm talking about the fact that
赶出我的公司后
you're sitting pretty in this firm
舒舒服服地坐在自己的公司里这事
after you forced me out of mine.
我只把你撵出去算你走运
You're lucky that's all I did,
因为你要为数名囚犯的死亡负责
because you're responsible for the deaths of multiple inmates.
-你空口无凭  -弗兰克·加洛供认的
- According to you. - According to Frank Gallo.
对  你让他在摄像头前说
That's right, you got him on tape saying
我们干了多么可怕的事
what monsters we all are.
然后你用录像来威胁我
And then you used it to blackmail me
提前退休
into early retirement.
但退休给了我充足的思考时间
But that gave me plenty of time to think.
弗兰克·加洛为什么会和你们合作
Why the hell would Frank Gallo cooperate with you
他可是承认了谋杀罪啊
if it meant admitting to murder?
你想说什么  汤米
What are you getting at, Tommy?
你和律所给弗兰克·加洛钱
You and this firm offered Frank Gallo money
让他留给他女儿
for his daughter
好让他做伪证
in exchange for fabricated testimony
然后你可以用它来要挟我
that you used to leverage me.
现在我来找你算账了
Now I'm here to make you pay.
你是来找我们复仇
You're coming at us to get revenge
为你的确犯过的罪
for something you actually did.
我是来讨回你们欠我的东西的
I'm coming at you for what's owed to me,
也就是我失去律所的赔偿
which is the compensation for the firm that I lost.
你又要怎么补偿
And how about you compensate the families
你所杀害的人的家人呢
of the people that you had killed?
你唯一应得的
Because the only thing that you are owed
就是一副镣铐
are a pair of prison stripes.
你要是起诉我们  我保证你会戴上的
And if you do this, I promise you'll get them.
罗伯特  我想听虚言恫吓的话
Robert, if I wanted empty threats,
我还不如直接带这个去找哈维呢
I would have brought this right to Harvey.
我没去找他  因为我想在这里
But I didn't, because I wanted to be here
看看你意识到我要像你们击败我一样
to see the look on your face when you realized
把你们统统干掉时
I'm going to take you all down...
脸上的表情
just like you did to me.
*看到钱  就愿意留下吃饭*
* See the money, wanna stay for your meal *
*给你太太再拿块馅饼*
* Get another piece of pie for your wife *
*所有人都想知道那感觉*
* Everybody wanna know how it feel *
*所有人都想见见那景象*
* Everybody wanna see what it's like *
*豆子馅饼我也愿吃  我不在乎*
* I'll even eat a bean pie, I don't mind *
*我和妹子忙着赚钱*
* Me and Missy is so busy, busy making money *
*好了*
* All right *
*退开点  我要跳舞*
* All step back, I'm 'bout to dance *
诉讼双雄  第八季  第九集
*美钞爵士摇摇摇*
* The greenback boogie *
说白了
Let me get this straight.
汤米·布莱顿要以共谋起诉我们
Tommy Bratton is accusing us of conspiracy
并要求两千万赔偿金
and suing us for $20 million.
朝我们勒索两千万
Blackmailing us for $20 million.
你们想怎么说都行
Call it whatever you want.
我反正不会给那孙子一分钱
I'm not giving that son of a bitch one nickel.
我们要怎么做  罗伯特
Well, what are we going to do, Robert?
因为  虽然我不想这么说
Because, I hate to say it
但我们的确和你串谋了
-- we did conspire with you.
我来告诉你我们要做什么
I'll tell you what we're going to do.
我们要筛查那件案子前后
We're gonna go through every piece
我们每次对话的痕迹
of communication on that case
确保没有任何证据可以把我和律所联系起来
and make sure there's nothing linking me to this firm.
罗伯特  我是去你家谈的
Robert, I went to your house.
迈克是去你家谈的
Mike went to your house.
我们一封邮件都没发过  一通电话都没打过
We never exchanged one email, phone call.
我们安稳无虞
We're good.
我可不想把我的未来押注在你的回忆上
And I don't feel like risking my future on your memory.
等等
Wait a minute.
也许我们压根不用押注
Maybe we don't have to risk anything on anything.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
我说的是某个和布莱顿关系亲密
I'm talking about someone close to Bratton
他也许能把这麻烦扼杀在摇篮中
who might be able to stop this thing dead in its tracks.
-伊莱·古尔德  -没错
- Eli Gould. - Exactly.
他是布莱顿以前的合伙人
He was Bratton's partner,
更重要的是  亚历克斯有他的录音
and what's more-- Alex got him on tape
亲口承认自己做了可以吊销执照的事
admitting that he committed a disbarrable offense.
就是说你们手里一直
Which means you've been dangling a sword
捏着他的把柄
over his head ever since.
你猜怎么着  把柄就在这里
And guess what. I got the sword right here.
就这么定了  这就是我们的反击策略
That settles it. We have our game plan.
等等  如果这事闹上法庭
Hold on. If this thing goes to trial,
布莱顿有可能坐牢是吗
couldn't Bratton end up in prison?
你想说什么  唐娜
What are you getting at, Donna?
为什么他会赌上一切只为了报仇
Why would he risk that just to get revenge?
因为人在自以为走投无路时
Because people do crazy things
会做出疯狂的事
when they think they've lost everything.
现在行动吧
Now let's get to it.
我们都各自有活儿要干
We've all got something to do.
萨曼莎  不管是什么事  现在时机不合适
Samantha, whatever it is, now is not the time.
那太糟了  我们有麻烦了
Too bad. We have a problem,
他的名字叫盖文·安德鲁
and his name is Gavin Andrews.
他现在又想怎样
Oh, what now with that man?
长话短说  德克哈特保险集团
Long story short-- Dexhart Insurance
要告右舷航空公司
needs to sue Starboard Airlines.
这两家都是我们的客户
And how exactly is that supposed to happen
要怎么让这事实现
when we represent them both?
不然你以为我来这干什么
Why do you think I'm here?
你最好不是来让我通知
Oh, you better not be here to get me
亚历克斯放弃他的客户
to tell Alex to drop his client.
罗伯特  你知道盖文不值得我们费心
Robert, you know Gavin is not worth the headache.
-必须放弃他  -我有个更好的主意
- He needs to go. - Here's a better idea.
既然你和亚历克斯都刚失去了一个客户
Since you and Alex each just lost a client,
不如保住这两个
these two clients stay.
什么
What?
你以为我不知道兰德·考德那破事吗
You think I wouldn't find out about that Rand Kaldor shit?
-罗伯特  我打算  -听我说
- Robert, I was gonna-- - Listen to me.
律所正处在危险中  不能起内讧
This firm is under attack. We can't do this right now.
处在危险中  什么意思
What do you mean under attack?
不关你的事
That's none of your concern.
你只要留住这两个客户就可以了
What is your concern is fixing this situation.
但两方都不愿意妥协  我们该怎么办
And how do we do that when neither client is gonna back down?
我告诉你  你和亚历克斯不要再幼稚了
I'll tell you how--you and Alex stop acting like children.
让你们俩的客户坐下来和解
Get your clients in a room and get them to settle.
如果这个方案不成  那该怎么办
And what do you propose we do when that doesn't work?
萨曼莎  我没有功夫跟你在这扯嘴皮子
Samantha, instead of taking up more time that I don't have,
我建议你想办法把事搞定
I propose you make it work.
早上好  卡特里娜
Good morning, Katrina.
有什么能为你效劳的吗
Can I help you with something?
如果咱俩谈得顺利
If this conversation goes as planned,
你将能成为我的左膀右臂
you're going to be helping me with a lot of things.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我刚成了高级合伙人
I just made senior partner.
-正式决定了吗  -是的
- So it's official? - It's official.
我的第一步
And, as my first act,
布莱恩·西蒙·阿特曼
Brian Simon Altman,
你愿意成为我的新律师吗
will you be my associate?
卡特里娜  我很荣幸
Katrina, I'm honored.
但在我回答前
But before I answer,
你确定我俩这样密切合作
are you sure the two of us working so closely together
是个好主意吗
is a good idea?
什么
What?
我是说  我们是好朋友
I mean, we've become good friends,
如果我正式为你工作  事情可能变得复杂
so it might get complicated if I officially work for you.
谢谢你的周全考虑  布莱恩
I appreciate that, Brian,
但如果你可以我也没问题
but I'm okay with it if you are.
那我非常愿意成为你的新律师
In that case, I would love to be your associate.
我建议先订些基本规矩吧
Then I suggest we start with some ground rules.
首先  每天你都要来得最早
First, every day you get here before everyone else.
-没问题  -其次  只戴战斗领带
- Done. - Next, power ties only.
而不是之前你戴过的那些
Not any of the ties I have ever seen you wear.
我也正想给自己的领带来个大换血
I've been meaning to replace my entire collection anyway.
最后  我不要一个老好人
Finally, I don't want a yes-man.
不管是什么事情
So I don't care what the topic is--
如果你有异议  我希望你提出
if you disagree with me, I want you to push back
无论我是否生气
whether it'll piss me off or not.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
如果我说好  那我就成了老好人
If I say yes to that, that would mean I'm being a yes-man,
所以现在我有点不知所措
so I don't know what to do right now.
那我来告诉你
I'll tell you what you're gonna do.
你要帮我赢这案子  让我们一举成名
You're gonna help me win the case that's gonna put us on the map.
你有时间吗
Do you have a second?
除非你有时间读完那一大箱子资料
Only if you have an hour to go through that box over there.
事实上  我有更好的方法来打发我的时间
Actually, I think I may have a better way to spend my time.
行
Okay.
告诉我你的小脑袋在想什么
What's going on in that brain of yours?
刚才我不想在会议室说
I didn't want to say it in the room,
但我觉得伊莱·古尔德不应该
but I don't think Eli Gould is the only person
是我们唯一的策略
we should be going to right now.
我们还得去见下加洛的女儿
We need to pay a visit to Gallo's daughter.
你觉得她知道些能帮我们的东西
You think she knows something that can help us.
我不确定她知道什么
I don't know what she knows.
但我们最好搞清楚  因为有可能
But we better find out, because there's a chance
布莱顿也给她洗脑了
that Bratton has her in his pocket.
谁知道他用了什么手段骗到了她呢
And who knows what lies he told to get her there?
你是对的  我现在就去
You're right. I'll go there right now.
不不不  我正想告诉你这个
No, no, no. That's what I'm trying to tell you.
不能你去
It can't be you.
唐娜  我知道你属于律所领导层的一部分
Donna, I know you're a part of the firm's leadership, but--
哈维  如果布莱登给她洗脑了
Harvey, if Bratton has convinced her of some bullshit,
几乎不可能让她回心转意
then it's gonna be next to impossible to change her mind.
而把她父亲关起来的人
And the man who put her father away in the first place
更加做不到这点
isn't the one to do that.
你是对的  尽你所能吧
You're right. Do what you can.
终于找到你了
Oh, finally.
-我到处找你  -怎么了
- I've been looking for you. - Why?
你还有别的案子要放弃吗
You got another lawsuit to drop?
事实上  我想达成和解
Actually, I have a settlement to reach.
他们在咖啡里下了什么药
Are they putting something in this coffee?
听上去你好像妥协了
Because it sounds like you're backing off.
亚历克斯  罗伯特不希望
Alex, Robert doesn't want either one of us
我们谁再丢客户了
losing any more business right now.
你是说你想说服他让我放弃盖文  他不同意
You mean you asked him to make me drop Gavin, and he said no.
重要的是
The important thing is
保住双方的客户不是个请求
keeping both clients wasn't a request.
而是命令
It was an order.
也就是说我们要想办法不闹上法庭
Which means we need to figure out a way to stay out of court.
-是的  -这个嘛
- We do. - Well...
我不会为取悦罗伯特·赞恩卖我的客户
I'm not selling out my client just to please Robert Zane,
所以你建议怎么做
so what exactly are you suggesting?
我建议我们学习下好战之人的
I'm suggesting that we do what two people that like to go to war
妥协策略  想办法和解
sometimes have to do-- find a way to make peace.
伊莱
Eli.
我希望你不介意  你妻子让我进来的
I hope you don't mind-- your wife let me in.
路易·利特
Louis Litt.
你竟然还有脸来我家
You've got some balls coming to my house.
我知道你不喜欢
I knew you might not like it,
所以我给你带了礼物
which is why I brought you a gift.
这是我想的那个东西吗
Is that what I think it is?
如果你觉得这是唯一一份
If you think it's the only copy
那晚亚历克斯·威廉姆斯录下的录音
of the recording Alex Williams made of you that night,
没错  就是它
then, yeah, it is.
-我现在打算给你  -为什么
- And I'm offering it to you. - Why would you do that?
我想我们能达成某种协议
I thought we could work out a little arrangement.
你让汤米·布莱顿撤诉
You get Tommy Bratton to back off his lawsuit,
这个能让你失去律师资格的小东西就归你了
you get back the one thing that can cost you your license.
你凭什么认为我会为了
What makes you think I'd help you
把那玩意儿拿回来而帮你
just to get that damn thing back?
伊莱  我不认为你了解现状
Eli, I don't think you fully understand the situation.
也许是我们逼他退出的
We may have forced him out,
但他的名字还挂在你的墙上
but his name is still on your wall.
如果闹上法庭
You take this to court,
布莱顿·古尔德这个名字
you're risking the name Bratton Gould
很可能会一辈子和腐败谋杀扯上关系
forever being associated with corruption and murder.
当布莱顿说服陪审团
And when he convinces a jury
你们伪造证据并勒索他时
that you fabricated material just to blackmail him,
全世界都会知道你们是骗子
the whole world's gonna think you're liars.
你手里的录音一文不值
That little tape of yours will be worthless,
布莱顿·古尔德的名声不会受损
and the name Bratton Gould will be just fine.
伊莱  你得想清楚
Eli, you need to think this through.
-这个男人有罪  -他曾是我的合伙人
- The man is guilty. - The man was my partner.
你们敲诈了他几百万
You cost him millions,
还用这东西勒索了我两回
blackmailed me twice with that thing already,
现在轮到你们血债血偿了
and now you're gonna pay.
-伊莱  求你了  -从我家滚出去
- Eli, please. - Get the hell out of my house.
这真是胡闹
This is a bunch of bullshit.
我猜你已经熟悉案子了
I take it that means you're up to speed?
不仅是熟悉案子了
I'm not just up to speed,
还熟悉了很多这辈子都用不上的女装知识
I know more about women's clothing than I ever thought possible.
那你就知道高升时尚公司
Then you know Hi-Rise Fashion
一直在坑骗我们的客户
has been ripping off our client's designs.
是的  但我不知道如何阻止他们
I do. The thing I don't know is how we're gonna stop them,
因为版权法可是众所周知的模棱两可
because copyright laws are notoriously vague.
所以如果我们能赢  就能一举成名
Which is why when we win, it's going to make a statement.
既然我不能做老好人
Then since I'm not supposed to be a yes-man,
我得问问  你不觉得我们的第一案子
I have to ask--are you sure you don't want our first case
应该选稳赢的案子吗
to be a guaranteed win?
好吧  事实上我不仅想一举成名
Okay, the truth is I'm not just doing this to make a statement.
更是因为设计师是我的朋友
I'm also doing it because the designer is my friend.
所以这案子涉及私人恩怨
Which means this case is personal.
我答应自己当我有能力自己选案子时
And I told myself that when I had enough clout to pick my cases,
我会选她的
I would pick hers.
既然如此  不如告诉我第一步该怎么做
In that case, why don't you tell me what our first move is?
简单
Easy.
明早我们把这个甩给他们
Tomorrow morning we slap them with this.
-丹妮斯·加洛吗  -什么事
- Denise Gallo? - Yeah?
我叫唐娜·鲍尔森 冒昧问您几个问题
My name's Donna Paulsen. I'd like to ask you a few questions.
什么问题
About what?
是否有个叫托马斯·布莱顿的男人来找过您
I was wondering if a man named Thomas Bratton came to you
询问有关您父亲给您的钱的事
asking about the money you received from your father.
他来是问我从你那儿拿到的钱
He came to me to ask about the money I got from you.
你和他说了什么
And what'd you tell him?
我说我不知道我父亲是从哪拿到的这笔钱
That I don't know what my father did to get that money,
但有人到我家门口给我留了张支票
but a man came to my home and dropped off a check,
不拿白不拿呗
and I wasn't about to turn it down.
那个人没有告诉你
And didn't that man also tell you
你父亲是个好人吗
that your father was a good person?
说了又怎样
So what if he did?
那些人想证明
So these people are trying to say
是我们花钱雇他来骗人的
that we paid him off to lie for us.
这不是事实
And it isn't true.
你想让我干嘛
What do you want me to do about it?
我希望你能出庭作证
I want you to take the stand and testify.
你父亲是为了救赎自我而死的
Your father died trying to redeem himself.
他们想阻止你
They're trying to take that away from you,
你不能让他们得逞
and you can't let them do it.
算说我相信你
Let's say I believe you
弗兰克也改过自新了
and Frank actually had changed.
托马斯·布莱顿告诉我他死的原因
Thomas Bratton told me the reason he got killed
就是因为你
is 'cause of you.
你要否认吗
Are you gonna tell me that's not true?
不
No.
我不否认
I'm not.
因为他们可以向你撒谎  我不会
Because they might lie to you, but I won't.
若是我们没有联系他
Frank never would have tried to redeem himself
弗兰克也不会试图自我救赎
if we hadn't contacted him.
是的  他也许不会死
So, yeah, he might still be alive.
但他的死绝不是因为我们
But the reason he's dead isn't because of us.
而是因为他们杀了他
It's because they killed him.
无所谓了
Well, it doesn't matter...
因为我再也没法知道他要成为的人
'cause I never knew the man he became.
我只知道他过去的样子
I only knew the man he was,
一个撒谎成瘾
and that man would've lied, cheated,
为了目标不惜一切的人
done whatever else it took to get what he wanted,
大多数时候  那个目标是钱
which, most of the time, was money.
如果你要在证人席上这么问我
And if you ask me about that under oath,
这就是我全部的回答
that's all I'll be able to say.
路易  大家都在这  发生什么事了
All right, Louis, we're all here. What's going on?
古尔德那边行不通
It didn't work with Gould.
我也不想再说个坏消息
And I hate to pile on the bad news,
但如果布莱顿让丹妮斯·加洛作证的话
but if Bratton puts Denise Gallo on the stand,
她会说弗兰克·加洛
she's gonna say that Frank Gallo
从来都是爱财如命的人
never did a thing that wasn't for money.
那样就会让我们有买通他说谎的嫌疑
Which makes it look like we paid him off to lie.
而且就算我们真的这么做了
And if we did that,
我们还会有合谋的嫌疑
we'd also be willing to conspire with each other.
这么说我们又回到起点了
Which means we're right back at square one.
这可说不好
I wouldn't say that.
-你在这做什么  伊莱  -我有一个提议
- What are you doing here, Eli? - I'm here with an offer.
把录音带还给我  我会让他同意和解
Give me that tape back, I'll get him to settle.
给我五百万  加上你俩承认自己做的事
$5 million, and you two admit what you did.
-不行  -这能给你省钱
- No deal. - It saves you money.
但我们有可能因此丢掉执照
It also puts us in a position of losing our licenses.
这也是两年以来他加在我头上的梦魇
Which is what he's been holding over my head for two years.
我不管  这我不干
I don't give a shit. No deal.
我昨晚认真思考过你说的话
Look, I thought about what you said last night
但要说服汤米  我总得给他点好处
but if I'm gonna convince Tommy, I got to give him something.
签个民事诉讼自认  我们会保密的
Sign a civil admission, and we'll seal it.
要是签了那个  不管保密与否
Sealed or not, we sign something like that,
它总会有一天在法庭上出现
it finds its way to the Bar.
听着
Listen to me.
我和你一样不想再在此事上纠缠
I want this to go away as much as you,
但我要告诉你
but I'm telling you--
这是你最好的选择
this is the best you're gonna get.
我本不想这么说的
I hate to say this, but...
但我认为我们最好还是接受这个条件
I think maybe we should take his deal.
我们不能相信伊莱·古尔德
We can't trust Eli Gould.
汤米·布莱顿同样不可信
And we sure as hell can't trust Tommy Bratton.
你是不是忘了
And I think you're forgetting
就算他们在加洛的问题上撒了谎
that they may be lying about the Gallo part,
但你和罗伯特被他们抓的把柄是的确存在的
but you and Robert did what they're saying.
-那又怎样  -所以我们也许
- So what? - So we may have
别无选择  只有相信他
no other choice than to trust him.
我屁都不信
I'm not trusting shit.
因为我现在明白这局棋是怎么走的了
Because I know what's going on here.
这全和唐娜最初的问题有关
And it goes back to Donna's original question.
你是说为什么一个像汤米·布莱顿这样的男人
You mean why would a man like Tommy Bratton
会冒吃牢饭这个险吗
risk going to prison?
答案就是他不会
And the answer is he wouldn't.
这就是一套好警察坏警察的虚张声势的把戏
This whole thing is a good-cop-bad-cop bluff,
-我要亲手把它解决了  -怎么解决
- and I'm gonna put a stop to it. - How?
用解决恶霸的方式来
The way you put a stop to any bully.
你接受挑战  让他自食恶果
You take his bluff, and you shove it down his throat.
真漂亮  谁设计的
Those are lovely. Whose are they?
-您这是什么意思  -她是问您谁是设计师
- I'm sorry? - She means who designed them,
因为我们知道不是你们的人
since we know your people didn't.
就像你们也没有设计这个
Just like they didn't design this
这个  或这个
or this or this.
我不知道你们是什么人
I don't know who you are,
但这些全部是我们去年春装系列的一部分
but these items were all part of our last spring line,
是我们自己设计的
and we designed them ourselves.
你说的该是你抄袭我委托人的吧
What you mean is you copied my client's designs,
逼她退出市场  降低价格
then beat her to market and undercut her price.
我懂了
I see what this is...
我见过你们这种人
because I've seen it before.
二流律所的新律师
And no associate at some middling law firm
可勒索不了我
is going to shake me down.
我可不是什么新律师  我是高级合伙人
I'm not an associate, I'm a senior partner.
这个不是什么勒索
And this isn't a shakedown
这是我们在法庭上让你一败涂地之前
it's a chance at a settlement
一次和谈的机会
before we clean you out in court.
想打官司就打去吧
Then file your suit,
抄袭和灵感之间只有一线之隔
because it's a thin line between theft and inspiration,
特别是在创意产业
particularly in a creative industry
人人都可能有相似的思路
where people have similar ideas all the time.
我的律师已经向我确认过这一点了
My lawyers have assured me of that.
他们是否与您提过
Have they also told you about
约翰森诉奥林匹亚唱片公司一案
Johnson v. Olympia Records?
因为有位作曲家可是得到了一千五百万的赔偿
Because a songwriter was awarded $15 million
因为作品被剽窃  与现在的情况非常相似
for plagiarized work in exactly the same situation.
因为有过跨行业的先例
And since precedents can cross industries,
特别是在创意产业
in particular the creative ones...
我们认为给予一千五百万的补偿是合理的
We thought $15 million for our client's designs would be fair.
我们会给你24小时与律师商议的时间
We'll give you 24 hours to consult your lawyers.
要是过了  我们就在法庭上见吧
After that, we'll see you in court.
作为律师  我们的职责是为你们赴汤蹈火
As your lawyers, it is our job to go to war for you.
大多数时候  这意味着上法庭
Most of the time that means going to court.
但事实上  法庭是丑恶  腐败的
The thing is, court is ugly, expensive,
最主要的  还有很大的风险
and, most of all, it's risky.
昨晚萨曼莎和我想到了一个办法
So last night Samantha and I came up with a way
来避免这些
to avoid all that.
我们所说的这幅画
The painting in question
市场价格超过一亿两千万
had a market value of $120 million.
我们提议右舷航空支付百分之四十五的赔偿金
Our proposal is that Starboard Airlines pay 45%,
但不承担过失责任
with no admission of fault.
我们摊开了说
Let me get this straight.
你想让我支付五千万
You want me to pony up $50 million
来对莫须有的罪名作出赔偿
when we didn't do anything wrong?
盖文  这是一种让步
Gavin, it's a compromise.
双方都得付出一些代价
There's got to be pain on both sides.
我怎么觉得我的代价远远大于
Well, I say that's a lot of pain on mine
对方的代价呢
and not enough on theirs.
现在的形势对你来说是百分之百有利
And you've got exposure for the full 120,
要我说  你可捡到宝了
so I'd say you're getting a hell of a deal.
你说的话对我毫无意义
Well, I don't really care what you say.
那我说  要说谁能在这案子上受益
Then I'll say it. If anybody's coming out ahead here,
那是你  你以为我乐意吗
it's you, and I don't like it.
-妮娜  你听我说  -不  我听过了
- Nina, listen to me. - No, I did listen to you--
两天前  当你告诉我这个狗娘养的
two days ago, when you said this shady son of a bitch
故意损毁了那幅画
destroyed that painting intentionally
你还拿出了证据
and you'd prove it.
-我不信  -"狗娘养的"
- I don't believe it. - "Shady son of a bitch"--
你就是这么称呼你的前委托人的吗
is that how you talk about your former clients?
-盖文  -没错  她就是这么说的
- Gavin-- - Yeah, that's what she said.
妮娜  我们现在把钱的事摆到桌面上谈
Nina, this deal puts money on the table now.
你要是不接受  我会坚持上诉到2020年
You don't take it, I will appeal this thing till 2020
不费吹灰之力
and not break a sweat.
假设我们不推翻  而且我们能推翻的
Assuming we don't get it tossed, which we will,
根据我对你和你的公司的办事风格的了解
knowing what I do about how you and your company do business.
我的办事风格
About how I do business?
你就这么眼睁睁地让他说了算
You gonna let him push us around like that?
亚历克斯  这案子要输了
Alex, this thing is a loser for you.
让你的委托人控制一下自己
Get your client under control.
别在我对委托人的态度上指手画脚
Don't tell me how to handle my client
是你挑起这件事的
when you started this whole thing.
也别告诉我这个案子会输
And don't talk to me about this case being a loser.
-我们走到这一步是你走运  -放屁
- You're lucky we're even in here. - Bullshit.
是你走运
You're lucky we're in here.
我们要是上了法庭  你一定会输的哭爹喊娘
We go to court, and I will clean your clock.
-放马过来  -老娘不怕
- Bring it on. - If only we could.
在我看来  我们上法庭好了
As far as I'm concerned, you can,
因为我实在是受够了
'cause I've had enough of this.
你要钱  萨曼莎  有种来拿
You want my money, Samantha, come and take it,
我拒绝签任何协议
'cause I'm not signing any deals with anyone.
哈维  我们能谈谈吗
Harvey, can I talk to you for a second?
谈什么
What about?
谈谈我受够了
About the fact that I've had it
萨曼莎·惠勒的胡说八道
with Samantha Wheeler's bullshit.
等等  发生什么了
Slow down. What's going on?
她有意怂恿
What's going on is she deliberately encouraged
德克哈特保险集团向我的当事人提起诉讼
Dexhart Insurance to sue my client,
我没法这么小心翼翼下去了
and I'm tired of tiptoeing around the situation.
你的意思是
Meaning?
我想和她在法庭上对峙
I want to go toe-to-toe with her in trial.
你是想让我们律所代表双方出庭对峙
You want us to go to trial representing both clients?
哈维  今天我和两方委托人都在场
Harvey, I was in a room with all sides today.
没有人肯让步
They want a fight as much as I do.
他们会签利益冲突弃权书
They'll waive conflict.
亚历克斯  我们
And that would work, Alex,
现在不能在全世界面前
except we can't afford having two partners
让我们的两名律师决一死战
fighting a death match in front of the whole world,
尤其当我们需要看起来很团结的时候
when we need to look unified.
什么叫我们需要看起来很团结
What do you mean when we need to look unified?
发生什么了
What's going on?
我不想说  但是我们正在处理
I don't want to get into it, but we're handling it.
事实是  哈维  我们并不团结
Well, here's the thing, Harvey--we're not unified.
就算我们是  那两个委托人也不会和解的
And even if we were, those two clients aren't going to settle.
所以不管你愿不愿意  我下一步是上法庭
So, like it or not, my next move is going to court
把她踢出这个案子
to get her kicked off this case.
萨曼莎  如果你是为了
Samantha, if you're here about your case
右舷航空的案子来
against Starboard Airlines--
-你听说了  -我是冠名合伙人
- You know about that? - I'm a name partner.
我们的一位律师要起诉我们的另一位律师
It's my business to know when one of our attorneys
我怎么会不知道
files suit against another.
我们在上诉的时候
Well, while we're on the subject of filing things,
亚历克斯·威廉姆斯提出了这个
Alex Williams filed this.
这是要强迫你退出案子
This is a motion to force you to recuse yourself.
他想把我踢出案子
Yeah, he's trying to get me kicked off my own case,
所以你要把他踢出去
which means you're gonna kick him off instead.
-等等  你说什么  -你听到了
- Wait, what? - You heard me.
亚历克斯将放弃盖文·安德鲁
Alex is gonna drop Gavin Andrews,
而你要让他这么做
and you're gonna make him do it.
不  你想让他放弃  你去找罗伯特
No. You want that done, you go to Robert.
罗伯特不在  我需要这件事立马有结果
Robert's not here, and I need it done now.
我没法帮你
Well, I can't do it for you.
你可以  而且你会帮我  这是你欠我的
You can and you will because you owe me.
你不能拿之前我欠你的  来要求我做这事
Oh, no. You don't get to call in that chit for this.
我可以要求你做任何事
I get to call it in for whatever I want,
因为是你来找我  让我放弃德尔塔
because you came to me and made me drop Delta,
当你从罗伯特那里
and then I went against Robert
拿回你的案子时我违背了罗伯特的意思
when you wanted back on the case he took from you.
所以管你愿不愿意  都要甩掉盖文·安德鲁
So we are dropping Gavin Andrews whether you like it or not.
你来蒸桑拿吗
You come here for the steam?
很不想告诉你
Because I hate to break it to you,
但是你得把西装脱了
but you got to take the suit off.
很好笑  汤米
That's a good one, Tommy.
但我是来告诉你
But I'm here to tell you I don't care
我不关你选伊莱·古尔德  圣人还是甘地
if you get Eli Gould or Mother Teresa or Gandhi
来当你的说客  我们不会接受你的协商
to be your good cop, we're not taking your deal.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
-我没有提出协商  -你有
- I didn't offer you a deal. - Oh, yes, you did.
因为你没有胆量冒坐牢的风险
Because you don't have the balls to risk going to prison.
真好笑  因为当我
That's funny, because what are you going to say
把你放在证人席上  直接了当地问你
when I put you on the stand and I ask you point-blank,
你是否和哈维·斯佩克特合谋  你能说什么
did you conspire with Harvey Specter?
你敢说大话
You talk a big game,
但事情不会如你所愿  因为我会说
but it's not going down like that, because I'm gonna say
你密谋陷害他人
that you conspired to keep people in prison
为了中饱私囊
for the purpose of lining your own pockets.
当你锒铛入狱
And when you end up in prison yourself,
里面的每个囚犯都会知道
every inmate in there is gonna know
你干的好事
that's exactly what you did.
现在谁在说大话了  罗伯特
Now who's talking a big game, Robert?
我
I am...
因为我们会出示
because we're gonna show this video
弗兰克·加洛把你供出来的视频
of Frank Gallo calling you out.
我们甚至可以把它传到油管上
Hell, we might even put it up on YouTube.
你大错特错  罗伯特
You're making a big mistake, Robert.
有胆你就试试
I'm calling your bluff.
撤诉吧
So drop this thing...
或者继续下去  选个审判日
or go ahead and pick a trial date.
但是汤米  提醒你一下  入狱后的日子
But, Tommy, just to be clear-- when they close that cell door,
可不好过
you're not gonna last the night.
哈维  我们得谈谈
Harvey, we need to talk.
如果是关于罗伯特和布莱顿
If it's about Robert and Bratton,
我还没收到答复
I haven't heard back yet.
不是  是关于亚历克斯和萨曼莎
It's not. It's about Alex and Samantha.
-亚历克斯又想做什么  -是萨曼莎
- What did he do now? - Not him, it's her.
她想让我逼亚历克斯放弃盖文·安德鲁
She wants me to make him drop Gavin Andrews.
那你他妈在这里做什么
Well, then what the hell are you doing in here?
拒绝她就好了
Just tell her no.
事情是这样的  哈维
Here's the thing, Harvey.
我欠她一个人情
I gave her a chit. I owe her.
她心知肚明  我现在不知道该做什么
She knows it, and now I don't know what to do.
-亚历克斯是对的  -什么意思
- Alex was right. - What do you mean?
我受够萨曼莎的扯淡了
I mean I've had about enough of Samantha's bullshit.
你是说我应该牺牲我的名誉
So you're saying I should sacrifice my honor
不兑现我的承诺
and not let her cash in her chit?
不  路易  恰恰相反
No, Louis. I'm saying the complete opposite.
卡特里娜  我们已经看了一整天了
Katrina, we've been going over this all day.
我们已经搞定他们了  他们会接受条件的
We've got them. They're gonna take the deal.
也许
Maybe they will,
但我还想再找更多确切的证据
but I am going to keep dotting my Is and crossing my Ts
我要确保万无一失
because I need to be sure.
你需要的不是一个应声虫
What you need is for someone not to be your yes-man,
-从现在开始  -布莱恩
- and that starts right now. - Brian--
卡特里娜  你刚成为高级合伙人
Katrina, you just became senior partner.
我打赌你连去庆祝的时间都没有
I bet you haven't even taken time to celebrate yet.
-我在赢了之后会去庆祝  -不  你不会
- I'll celebrate after we win. - No, you won't...
因为还会有下一个案子  在下一个案子
because there'll be another case and then another.
如果你不停下脚步
And if you don't stop
在重要的时刻到来之际好好珍惜
and appreciate the big moments when they come,
你会后悔的
you'll regret it.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
我在说我要摆摆前辈的架子
I'm saying I'm pulling rank.
我们出去庆祝  就是现在
We're going out to celebrate, and we're going out right now.
你以为  你以为你在做什么
What the ---- do you think you're doing?
亚历克斯  冷静一下
Whoa, Alex, calm down.
你告诉我的客户
You told my client
我们要放弃他  你还想让我冷静
we're dropping him and you want me to calm down?
我没把你打倒在地上你就该偷着笑了
You're lucky I'm not putting you on the floor right now.
听我说  我不得不这么做
Listen to me. I had to do it.
这是唯一的办法
It was the only way.
什么唯一的办法  让我丢脸的办法吗
The only way to what? Screw me over?
亚力克斯  我欠萨曼莎一个人情
Alex, I owed Samantha.
偿还这个人情唯一的办法就是帮她做这个
The only way for me to get out of it was to do this for her.
-也就是说你心中她更重要  -不是这样
- So you put her over me. - No, I didn't.
因为如果她不问我要这个
Because if she wasn't asking for this,
她就要让我支持她成为冠名合伙人
she'd be asking me to back her for name partner
到时候  就不是像现在这样
when the time comes, instead of me and Harvey backing you
有我和哈维支持你
for name partner right now.
你是说我是冠名合伙人
You're telling me I'm name partner?
我可没得到消息
Because I didn't get the memo.
现在  哈维就在和赞恩谈
Harvey's going to Zane as we speak.
好吧  路易  我的名字一旦印门上
Well, Louis, the second you put my name on the door,
我就和盖文打电话告诉他  他被抛弃了
I will call Gavin and drop him like a hot potato.
在那之前  他还是我的客户
Until then, he's my client,
你可不要在我不知情的情况下再联系他了
and don't you ever contact him without my knowledge again.
致赞恩-斯佩克特-利特最新的高级合伙人
To Z.S.L.'s newest senior partner.
布莱恩  你已经向我敬过四次酒了
Brian, you've already toasted me four times.
我以为你很少参加这种庆祝活动
I figured you're new to this whole celebrating thing.
我想给你展示正确的做法
I wanted to show you how it's done.
要是这样的话
Well, in that case...
致赞恩-斯佩克特-利特律所最好的助理律师
to Z.S.L.'s best associate,
因为  布莱恩
because, Brian,
那个先例真是神来之笔
that precedent was a stroke of genius.
谢谢
Thank you.
顺便问一句  你是怎么想到的
By the way, how did you come up with it?
音乐行业是完美的类比
The music industry is the perfect parallel,
然而之前从未有人想到这一点
and yet no one's ever thought of it before.
其实这事有点尴尬
It's actually a little embarrassing.
尴尬  什么意思
What do you mean embarrassing?
我想到音乐行业
I thought about the music industry
是因为我以前考虑过去当歌曲作家
because I considered becoming a songwriter myself.
-你在开玩笑嘛  -不
- You're kidding. - No.
事实上  朱莉和我讨论了很久
In fact, Julie and I talked about it a long time
我才决定去读法学院
before finally deciding on law school.
让我猜猜看
Let me guess.
她想让你选择更保险的道路
She wanted you to take the safer route,
而你想探索自己的艺术
and you wanted to explore your artistic side.
实际上是反过来的
Actually, the other way around.
我和她说我要当律师的时候
When I told her I was going to be a lawyer,
她说我应该对自己作为艺术家的才能更有信心
she said I should have more faith in myself as an artist.
有一个这么相信你的人  你真的很幸运
You're lucky to have someone who thinks so highly of you.
是的
I am.
但是  我投入法律后
But the thing is, once I moved into law,
我发现我对法律的爱和对写歌的爱是一样的
I found I loved it as much as I ever loved writing.
什么
What?
没什么  只是
Nothing. It's just...
朱莉不理解这一点
Julie doesn't understand that,
有时候我希望她能
and sometimes I wish she would.
不管怎么说  和一个对法律有兴趣的人
Anyway, it's nice to be able to talk about the law
聊天感觉还是很好的
with someone that's actually interested.
如果你有兴趣的话
Well, if that's what you're looking for,
我很乐意随时和你谈论法律的精微玄妙之处
consider me happy to discuss the nuances of the law anytime,
因为我对法律的热爱和你一样
because I love it as much as you do.
今晚谢谢你了  布莱恩
Thank you for tonight, Brian.
这正是我需要的
This is exactly what I needed.
谢谢你选我当你的助理律师  卡特里娜
Thanks for asking me to be your associate, Katrina.
我很高兴你问我
I'm really happy you did.
哈维  好
Oh, Harvey. Good.
你可以帮我过一遍这些档案
You can help me go through the last of these files.
我不会帮你看任何东西  罗伯特
I'm not going through anything, Robert.
我们得先谈谈亚历克斯·威廉姆斯
Not until we've talked about Alex Williams.
如果我猜的没错
If this is about what I think it is,
我们已经谈论过这件事了
we already talked about it.
不  我们当时同意搁置争议
No, we agreed to kick the can down the road.
现在  时间到了  因为我和路易
Well, this is the end of the road, because Louis and I
都支持亚历克斯成为合伙人
are backing Alex for name partner right now.
哈维  现在不是讨论这个的时候
Harvey, now is not the time to be discussing this.
不  正是时候
Yes, it is,
因为萨曼莎和亚历克斯要开战了
because Samantha and Alex are about to go to war.
如果你是说德克哈特保险集团的事
If you're talking about Dexhart Insurance,
我和她说和解
I told her to settle.
问题是  她没这么做
Well, she didn't.
她去找路易
She went to Louis,
用他欠的人情压他放弃盖文·安德鲁
called in a chit to make him drop Gavin Andrews.
我让你做执行合伙人
And I didn't let you become managing partner
不是为了方便你的兵去开战...
just so your lieutenant-- could start
不是你让我做的
You didn't let me do anything.
而且如果萨曼莎真这么做了  我会去处理
And if Samantha did that, I'll deal with her.
怎么处理
How?
因为在我看来  你从没处理过她
Because as far as I can tell, you have never dealt with her.
-够了  你听我说  -不  你听我说
- Okay, you listen to me. - No, you listen to me.
自从她来了之后  你让她为所欲为
You've let her do whatever she wants ever since she got here.
亚历克斯来了之后一直在为这家律所打拼
Alex has been fighting for this firm ever since he got here.
我向他保证过...
And I made him a promise--
你俩先别吵了  我们遇到更大的麻烦了
Before you two go any further, we got a bigger problem.
汤米·布莱顿没有虚张声势
Tommy Bratton wasn't bluffing.
他刚送达了开庭日期  从今天算起一周后
He just sent over a trial date. It's for a week from today.
-该死  -没错
- Shit. - Exactly.
所以你俩不能继续斗了
So you two need to stop fighting each other
-因为我们得一起对付他  -不  我们不用
- because now we got to fight him. - No, we don't.
因为我知道布莱顿这么做的原因
Because I know why Bratton's doing this.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
你以为布莱顿不会为这事冒进监狱的险
You thought Bratton wouldn't risk going to prison for this.
他会的  而且我知道为什么
Well, he will, and I know why.
我不知道你是什么情况
I don't know about you,
但早上七点带着宿醉到这里可不容易
but getting here at 7:00 a.m. isn't as easy with a hangover.
我不在乎  布莱恩
I don't care, Brian,
因为高升时尚刚刚扔了个炸弹
because Hi-Rise Fashion just dropped a bomb.
等等  什么  我们明明搞定他们了
Wait, what? How? We've got them.
在庭上  确实
In court, yes.
但他们刚刚和我们的制造商达成了一笔大交易
But they just cut a huge deal with our manufacturer.
然后忽然之间我们的制造商就告诉我们
And suddenly our manufacturer is telling us
他们没能力承接我们的产品了
they no longer have the capacity to handle our product.
你是说他们制约了他们的订单
You mean they made it a condition of their order,
这是违法的
which is illegal.
没错  确实
Yes, it is.
他们这么对我们  一定也这么对其他人了
And if they did it to us, they did it to others.
我会告诉他们  如果他们不收手的话
And I'm going to tell them I'm going to the DOJ
我就去向司法部举报
if they don't back off.
不行  没有证据就威胁他们的话
No, without proof a threat like that
可能会被认为是诱导恶意起诉
can be construed as inducing malicious prosecution.
-你不能这么做  -我必须得做点什么
- You can't do it. - Well, I have to do something.
因为我昨晚本应该把时间花在
Because instead of spending my time last night
思考如何防止这种事情上
thinking about how to prevent this,
但我却把心思放在了别处
I took my eye off the ball.
卡特里娜  别这么苛责自己
Katrina, don't be so hard on yourself.
你也没办法预见这种事情
You couldn't have seen this coming.
我本可以预见的
I might have seen it coming
如果我像计划中那样留在这里
if I'd stayed here like I wanted to
而不是被你说服去参加派对
instead of letting you convince me to go party.
等等  你的意思是这是我的错吗
Hold on a second. You're saying this is my fault?
我不是说服你  而是邀请你
Because I didn't convince you, I invited you.
而且你说你想找一个能够直话直说的律师
And you said you wanted an associate who would push back.
在案子上直话直说  而不是干扰我的工作
Push back on case work-- not tell me not to do my job.
那现在就让我直话直说
Then let me push back right now,
因为如果你这样吓唬这些人
because you bluff these guys,
你就会把自己暴露在风口浪尖了
you're opening yourself up to huge exposure.
那又怎样
So what?
哈维·斯佩克特整天虚张声势
Harvey Specter bluffs all the time.
哈维·斯佩克特有着超过15年的
Harvey Specter has a 15-plus-year track record
不败纪录
of kicking people's asses.
所以你不相信我能搞定这事
So you don't have faith in me to pull this off.
我不是这个意思  我是说这个险不值得冒
I didn't say that. I'm saying it's not a risk worth taking,
我不会让你这么做的
and I'm not gonna let you do it.
布莱恩  有时候是要直话直说
Well, Brian, there's a time to push back
但有时候也得注意分寸
and a time to get in line.
我今天下午3点钟过去
I'm going over there at 3:00 p.m. today,
你可以选择跟我去或者不去
and you are either with me or you're not.
我不去
Then I'm not,
因为这是个错误  你心里也清楚
because this is a mistake, and you know it.
哈维  有时间吗
Harvey, you have a minute?
我正准备起草几份动议
I'm about to file a few motions,
但可以  我有时间
but, yeah, I have a minute.
我怎么记得
I was under the impression
你一般不会亲自起草动议
you don't normally file your own motions.
这次比较重要
Well, it's kind of important.
有什么事吗
What's on your mind?
在高级合伙人的世界里遇到麻烦了
Trouble in senior partner town?
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
因为这是你进入高级合伙人的世界后
Because that's the first thing that happens
遭遇的第一件事
after you make it to senior partner town.
那么  长话短说...
Well, then long story short...
这是我的第一个案子
it's my first case,
我已经走投无路了  唯一的出路就是虚张声势
my back's against the wall, and my only way out is to bluff.
但是
But?
我会把自己处于风口浪尖  而且...
I'm opening myself up to significant exposure, and...
我不确定我能搞的定
I'm not sure I can pull it off.
-那就另想它法  -怎么想
- Then think of another way. - How come?
因为如果你不确定  说明你搞不定
Because if you're not sure you can pull it off, you won't.
而且  卡特里娜  人生很长
And, Katrina, life is long.
你不会希望一当高级合伙人就处于风口浪尖的
You don't want to start your senior partnership with exposure.
我得走了
Now, I got to go.
谢谢你  哈维
Thank you, Harvey.
他们把你的旧办公室给你了
I see they're letting you use your old office.
先是罗伯特  现在你又来了
First, Robert, now you?
他有他说话的权利
Well, he had his turn at bat.
我们觉得我也该有个说话的机会
We thought it was time for me to have mine.
那就出招吧
Oh, go ahead and take your best shot,
但如我和罗伯特说的  我不是吓唬你们
but like I told Robert, I'm not bluffing.
问题就在这儿  汤米  我们知道
That's the thing, Tommy, we know you're not,
而且我们知道原因
and we figured out why.
你根本不知道自己在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
我知道
Yes, I do.
原来三个月前  你检查出了癌症
Turns out, three months ago, you were diagnosed with cancer
医生说你只剩一年了
and given a year to live.
要是你知道  那也就该清楚
Well, if you know that, then you also know
我绝不会和解
I'm never going to settle.
我清楚的是我们的庭审策略
What I know is what our trial strategy is gonna be.
请求延期
Motion to delay,
请求延期  请求延期
motion to delay, motion to delay.
正义的车轮转得很慢  汤米
The wheels of justice turn slowly, Tommy,
也就是说即使你赢了  你也看不到了
which means even if you win, you won't be here to see it.
你真是个混蛋
You really are a son of a bitch, aren't you?
不  这是你干得好事
No. You did this.
是你自作自受
You brought this on yourself.
该放手了
It's time to let it go.
剩下的时间去陪陪家人
Spend what time you have left with your family.
让我回公司九个月
Just let me go back to my firm for nine months more,
我就撤诉
and I will drop this.
我拒绝  汤米
I can't let you do that, Tommy,
因为我知道你的行事方式
because I've seen what you do.
我不能让你重回战场
I'm not gonna let you get back in the game
再对别人做出这种事
and do something like this to someone else.
那我告诉你  你随便延期
Then you know what? Delay all you want.
因为他们说当你有很想得到的东西
Because they say when you're fighting something like I am,
也就有了活下去的动力
you have to have something to live for.
凭我对你的仇恨我就能活两年
Well, you just gave me two years to live on hate alone.
你给我出去  我们法庭见
Now get the hell out of here, and I'll see you in court.
这看起来像你助理的活儿
That looks like a job for your associate.
如果你只是来劝我不要唬人的
If you're just here to talk me out of my bluff,
不用担心  我放弃了
you don't have to worry-- I'm not gonna do it.
很好
Good...
因为你不用放弃了
because you don't have to.
难以置信
I don't believe it.
你拿到了他们和我们制造商合谋的证据
You got proof they colluded with our manufacturer.
是的
I did.
-布莱恩  你怎么做到的  -简单
- Brian, how did you get this? - Simple.
我打电话给工厂
I called up the factory
假装高升时尚公司合同部的人
pretending to be in Hi-Rise's contracts department
跟他们抱怨我们签订的
and started complaining about how all we had
只是他们答应的口头协议
were verbal assurances they'd uphold our agreement.
最终他们同意出书面记录
Eventually they agreed to sign a memo.
他们同意了承认罪状
They agreed to incriminate themselves?
也不是
Not exactly.
我跟他们说版权法说法暧昧
I told them copyright laws are notoriously vague,
他们的记录也可以暧昧
so their memo could be, too.
但一个暧昧的记录就足以
But even a vague memo is enough for us
让我们申请调查他们了
to get them investigated.
或者威胁说要调查
Or threaten to.
但现在
But now...
你可以拿证据威胁他们了
you can do it with proof.
你有没有想过冒充他人身份
Did it occur to you that misrepresenting yourself
你是要冒很大风险的
like this could have opened you up to huge exposure?
想了
It did.
但我觉得值得冒险
But I decided it was worth the risk,
因为我的工作不只是当个盾牌
because my job may be to push back,
还要做你的后盾
but it's also to have your back.
从今往后  我都会是
And from now on, I will.
光凭仇恨活两年
"Two more years on hate alone."
他真这么说了
He said that?
不止说了  还是认真的
He not only said it, the son of a bitch meant it.
他会跟我们斗到最后一口气
He's gonna fight us until his last breath.
怎么了
What?
当一个人被告知
A man gets told he only has
生命只剩下有限的时间
so much time left on this Earth,
一般都会产生新的人生感悟
you would think that would put things in perspective.
人会的
You would.
但前提是他得是人
But I guess he'd have to be human.
可是他更接近终结者
And as it turns out, he's more like the Terminator--
怎么打都打不死
just won't go down.
想活命就跟我走
Come with me if you want to live.
我还会回来的
I'll be back.
后会有期  宝贝
Hasta la vista, baby.
它能流血  我们就能杀它
If it bleeds, we can kill it.
首先  那是《捕食者》的台词
First of all, that's "Predator."
其次  你那是牙买加口音  不是德国口音
Second of all, you sound Jamaican, not German.
伙计  给我下来  伙计
Oh. Oh, man, get off my back, man.
告诉你  其实他是奥地利人
You know what? He's Austrian.
是啊
Yeah.
我们怎呢办
What are we gonna do?
我们别无选择
We're gonna do what we have to--
尽可能拖延
delay this thing as long as possible
想办法反击
and then fight it on its merits.
我们不用反击什么了
We don't have to fight anything anymore.
汤米·布莱顿死了
Tommy Bratton's dead.
什么
What?
伊莱·古尔德刚来了电话
Eli Gould just called.
说汤米心脏病发
Said Tommy had a heart attack.
他们认为是因为
They think it was brought on
和病魔的斗争压力很大
by the stress of fighting his illness.
还有和我们的斗争
And fighting us.
总之  不论如何
Anyway, for what it's worth,
古尔德要撤诉了
Gould's dropping the whole thing.
我得说  我知道我们一定会赢
I got to say, I always thought we'd win,
但没想到会这么赢
but not like this.
罗伯特  你没事吧
Robert, you okay?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们也许是在交战  但是
We may have been at war, but...
我认识那人三十年了
I knew the man for 30 years.
我需要点时间消化一下
I could use a minute to process this.
你需要多久都可以
You take all the time you need.
怎么样了
How'd it go?
之前不知道你喜欢棒球
I didn't know you liked baseball.
我也是第一次知道你爱音乐
I didn't know you liked music.
-今晚要回家吗  -是的
- You heading home for the night? - Yeah.
-其实我得...  -先别走
- Actually, I have to-- - Don't go yet.
布莱恩  这个案子你帮了我太多
Brian, you came through for me in every way on this case.
如你所说
And like you said the other night,
如果小事不庆祝
if we don't stop to celebrate the little things,
这一切又意义何在
then what's any of this for?
要不是我了解你
If I didn't know any better,
我会以为这是你感谢我
I'd say this is your way of thanking me
照顾你呢
for looking out for you.
是的
It is.
而且我给我们订了餐厅
And I happen to have made us reservations
是一家很棒的  有现场音乐的餐厅
at an amazing place with live music
为喜欢音乐的你订的
in honor of your love of music.
卡特里娜  今晚不行
Katrina, I can't tonight.
我真的得回家  朱莉和孩子在等我
I really need to get home to Julie and the baby.
孩子  没错
The baby, of course.
抱歉  是我没想到
I'm sorry. I didn't think about it.
没事的
No, it's okay.
你又没孩子  怎么会想到
If you don't have one, why would you think about it?
没错
Right.
这么说吧  我很希望下次补上
Let me just say that I would love to get a rain check.
-没问题  -那现在  我要走了
- Rain check it is. - In the meantime, I got to go.
你肯定能找到别人代替我的
I'm sure you have someone else who would love to take my place.
当然
Oh, of course.
晚安  布莱恩
Have a good night, Brian.
晚安  卡特里娜
Good night, Katrina.
打扰到你了吗
Am I interrupting?
-没有  -那就好
- Not really. - Good.
因为我昨晚碰巧打断了
Because I happen to have walked in
一段对话
on a conversation last night
让我觉得我该和你产生一段对话
that made me want to have a conversation with you.
我在听
I'm listening.
这个
This...
你和亚历克斯的事  已经愈演愈烈了
thing between you and Alex is coming to a head,
因为哈维和路易希望亚历克斯
because Harvey and Louis want Alex
当下一个冠名合伙人  罗伯特不同意
to be the next name partner and Robert doesn't.
别铺垫了  唐娜  你想说什么
Skip the preamble, Donna. What's on your mind?
我觉得请你让亚历克斯
I don't suppose it would do any good
先把名字放上去恐怕没什么用吧
to ask you to let this thing go and let Alex go up there first.
-难以置信  -什么
- I don't believe it. - Believe what?
哈维居然没胆自己来
That Harvey doesn't have the balls to come in here
跟我提要求  还派你来
and ask me that himself-- instead, he sent you.
他没派谁来  我是自己来的
He didn't send anybody. I'm here on my own.
那你可能已经接受了
Well, then you may have internalized
这里的父权制度  但我没有
the patriarchal system here, but I have not.
我没接受什么
I haven't internalized anything.
我说了  我来这里不是为某个男人
I told you, I'm not here at the behest of any man.
我是自己来  进行女人间的对话
I'm here on my own, woman-to-woman,
请求你把目光放长远  先等一等
asking you to take the long view and wait.
我相信你是这么想的  唐娜
I'm sure you think that's true, Donna,
但在来找我之前  你有想过
but did it occur to you to ask Alex to step down
去对亚历克斯做这个请求吗
before you came to me?
因为我说的父权指的是这个
Because that's what I mean by patriarchy.
我还真想了
Well, I did think to ask Alex,
而我选择了来找你
and I chose to ask you.
我之所以这么做  是因为说到底
And I did that because it comes down
问题在于是谁先得到了承诺
to who the promise was made to first,
而不是因为得到承诺的人的性别
not the gender of the person it was made to.
那在轮到我之前  谁能保证他们
And what's to stop them from changing their minds
不改变主意呢
before it's my turn?
因为至少要一年  他们才能
Because they're not gonna put a second name up there
再加一个名字
for at least another year.
要是他们出承诺书呢
What if they put it in writing?
你是个律师  把承诺书写到天衣无缝
You're a lawyer, you make it airtight.
你真是能让一个人
You really make a person get to the bottom
说出心底话  不是吗
of what's inside of them, don't you?
什么意思
What do you mean?
意思是你要这么说
I mean when you put it that way,
我得说这件事根本不事关他们会改主意
it's not about them changing their minds
或者等太久  甚至罗伯特出车祸都没事
or it taking too long or even Robert getting hit by a bus.
事实是
The truth is,
我不让步  是因为
I'm not backing down because...
我认为我比亚历克斯优秀
I think I'm better than Alex Williams.
而我绝不会承认事实并非如此
And I'm not going to say that I'm not.
那我尊重你的决定
Then I respect your decision.
晚安  萨曼莎
Good night, Samantha.
听说你赢了第一件案子
I heard you won your first case,
而我这么快就听说了的事实证明
and the fact that I already heard about it
你已经小有名气了
means you're already making a name for yourself.
所以
So...
谢谢  路易
Thank you, Louis.
等等  出什么事了吗
Wait a second. Is something wrong?
该死  他们是不是又少打了个字母
God damn it, did they spell Bennett with one T again?
不是  很完美
No, nothing's wrong.
只是今天事很多  我累了
It's just been a long day, and I'm tired.
卡特里娜  我了解你
Katrina... I know you.
刚赢了案子你才不会累
You don't get tired after winning a case.
你肯定不对劲
Something is going on.
只是  我知道我现在应该很开心
It's just...I know I should be happy right now.
我终于来到了我想要的顶峰
I finally made it to the top of the mountain.
我理解了  这让你意识到了你前面
I get it--it only made you realize how much further
还有多长的路要走
you still want to go.
是的  没错
Yes, that's it.
一点没错
That's exactly it.
不对
No, it's not it.
我见过这个表情  那是我的表情
I have seen that look before, and it was on my face.
卡特里娜
Katrina...
遇到这个生活问题的时候
when it comes to that part of life...
是不能勉强的
you can't force it.
这无法捉摸
It's unpredictable.
-我讨厌无法捉摸  -我知道
- I hate unpredictable. - I know.
我也是
I do, too.
但你曾经跟我说
But you once told me that someday,
我会找到另一半
I would find someone.
我也找到了
And I did.
你也会的
And you will, too.
命运会把那个特别的人
Life is gonna put that special someone
摆在你面前
right in front of you,
那个时候  我相信你会准备好的
and when it happens, I know you'll be ready.
我突然想起
Hey, I just realized...
我都没带你出去吃饭庆祝你升职呢
I never took you out to celebrate your promotion.
我们两个出去吃晚餐怎么样
What do you say we go out and get dinner right now?
下次吧  路易
Another time, Louis.
我还有事要办
I have some work to catch up on.
一个人喝酒啊
Drinking alone?
看来他们说的是真的
I guess what they say is true.
谁都不知道自己还剩多少时间
None of us know how much time we really have.
确实
No, we don't.
罗伯特  我一直在想
Listen, Robert, I've been doing some thinking
关于萨曼莎和亚历克斯的事
about the Samantha and Alex situation.
-今晚不说行吗  -听我说完
- Not tonight. - Just hear me out.
拜托
Please.
我觉得我应该让他们打一架
I think we should let them fight.
哈维  这样我们就是承认了公司分裂
Harvey, we do that, we're admitting our house is divided,
就更容易让汤米·布莱顿
and we make it that much easier
这样的人分裂我们了
for another Tommy Bratton to try and pick us apart.
我知道
I know.
但我们的公司已经分裂了
But our house is divided.
我做出了承诺  你也是
I made a promise, you made a promise.
如果我们继续袖手旁观
And if we keep doing nothing...
那比让他们自己解决还糟
It's worse than letting them settle it themselves.
一个案子  正面对决
One case, head-to-head,
赢家抱走冠名合伙人
winner gets name partner.
你觉得他们会答应吗
You think they'll go for it?
我觉得他们自从来了这里
I think they've been wanting to go at it
就一直想打一架了
ever since you two got here.
那我同意
Then I say we let them fight.
你想自己通知他们  还是我去
You want to tell them, or should I?
不如我们一起说
Why don't we both tell them?
但还是明天吧
But let's do it tomorrow.
因为今天之后  我只想喝杯酒
Because after today, all I want to do is finish this drink,
回家
go home, and...
见我的劳拉
see Laura.
晚安  罗伯特
Good night, Robert.
晚安  哈维
Goodnight, Harvey.